Guide to the Dr. Huey P. Newton Foundation Inc. Collection
Department of Special Collections
- Series 1: Huey P. Newton Papers, 1
  - Subseries 4: Education, 4
    - Peter Euben Course No. 203A Fall Quarter 19771977 (Box 40, Folder 6)
      "The Rise of a Non-Aristotelian System"
    - Lectures 1977- Euben 1977 - 1978 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Peter Euben Papers to Read [1 of 2]1977 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Peter Euben Papers to Read [2 of 2]1977 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Arthur Pearl Course No. 297 Winter Quarter 1978 Independent Study [including Newton's paper for the course on "New Educational Models"]1978 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      "New Educational Models"
    - Triloki Pandey Lectures 1978 Winter Quarter [1 of 2]1978 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Triloki Pandey Lectures 1978 Winter Quarter [2 of 2]1978 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Triloki Pandey Course No. 203B Winter Quarter 19781978 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      "Science, Codes, and Myths"
    - Papers to Read for Loki 1977-1978 [1 of 2] (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Papers to Read for Loki 1977-1978 [2 of 2] (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Triloki Pandey H.O.C. Course No. 277 Colloquium Overview Spring Quarter 1978 1978 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      Draft of "War on the Panthers: An Overview"
    - Dr. Eugenio Donato Course No. 203C - Spring Quarter 19781978 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      "Deconstructing the Object";"On Truth and Sanity"
    - Papers to Read for Eugenio Donato's Class (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Hegel, George --Hegel's Philosophy of Mind, p. 199 - 222 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - De Man, Paul --Nietzsche's Theory of Rhetoric" (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - De Man, Paul -- "International Structure of the Romantic Image" (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Nietzsche, Friedrich -- "On Truth and Falsity in their Unltramoral Sense" (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - The Evolution of Man in the African Continent (Summary)1966 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - The Island Colonies - Rural Poverty -- South Carolina 1970 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - [ "On Identity and Consciousness of El Hajj Malik El Shabazz (Malcolm X): An Application of the Theory of Identity to the History of Black Consciousness" by William Henry Moore] [1 of 3] 1974 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - [ "On Identity and Consciousness of El Hajj Malik El Shabazz (Malcolm X): An Application of the Theory of Identity to the History of Black Consciousness" by William Henry Moore] [2 of 3] 1974 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - [ "On Identity and Consciousness of El Hajj Malik El Shabazz (Malcolm X): An Application of the Theory of Identity to the History of Black Consciousness" by William Henry Moore] [3 of 3] 1974 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - [Vocal Mimicry]1985 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Citizen Participation Democracy and Social Change1969 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      Citizen Participation Democracy and Social Change by J. Herman Blake
    - 1979 Schedules and Meetings1978 - 1979 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - [Santa Cruz Papers and left magazines] [1 of 2] (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - [Santa Cruz Papers and left magazines] [2 of 2] (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Papers Done for Hayden White [1 of 4]1978 - 1979 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      "The Historical Origins of Existentialism and the Common Denominators of Existential Philosophy" ;""The Roots of Existential Philosophy in Western Thought" (draft)
    - Papers Done for Hayden White [2 of 4]1978 - 1979 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      "Common Denominators of Existential Philosophy" ;"The Historical Origins of Existentialism";"The Roots of Existential Philosophy in Western Thought" (draft)
    - Papers Done for Hayden White [3 of 4]1978 - 1979 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Papers Done for Hayden White [4 of 4]1978 - 1979 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - [The Narcotics "Cover"] [1 of 3] (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - [The Narcotics "Cover"] [2 of 3] (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - [The Narcotics "Cover"] [3 of 3] (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - [The War against the Panthers, by H. P. Newton - Preliminary Draft] [1 of 3]1978 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - [The War against the Panthers, by H. P. Newton - Preliminary Draft] [2 of 3]1978 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - [The War against the Panthers, by H. P. Newton - Preliminary Draft] [3 of 3]1978 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - [The War against the Panthers: A Study of Repression in America] [1 of 2]1979 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - [The War against the Panthers: A Study of Repression in America] [2 of 2]1979 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - [The War against the Panthers: A Study of Repression in America] [1 of 2]1979 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - [The War against the Panthers: A Study of Repression in America] [2 of 2]1979 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - The War against the Panthers: A Study of Repression in America [1 of 5]1979 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - The War against the Panthers: A Study of Repression in America [2 of 5]1979 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - The War against the Panthers: A Study of Repression in America [3 of 5]1979 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - The War against the Panthers: A Study of Repression in America [4 of 5]1979 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - The War against the Panthers: A Study of Repression in America [5 of 5]1979 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - [The War against the Panthers, by H. P. Newton] [1 of 3]1980 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - [The War against the Panthers, by H. P. Newton] [2 of 3]1980 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - [The War against the Panthers, by H. P. Newton] [3 of 3]1980 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - [Huey's dissertation] (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - [Document for UCSC, Bob Trivers' thesis - "Cocaine" by Craig Van Dyke] (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - [Documents for UCSC, Bob Trivers' thesis - Articles by Gary Marx] [1 of 4] (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - [Documents for UCSC, Bob Trivers' thesis - Articles by Gary Marx] [2 of 4] (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - [Documents for UCSC, Bob Trivers' thesis - Articles by Gary Marx] [3 of 4] (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - [Documents for UCSC, Bob Trivers' thesis - Articles by Gary Marx] [4 of 4] (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - [Document for UCSC, Bob Trivers' thesis - "Zoologiska Bidrag fran Uppsala"] [1 of 5] (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - [Document for UCSC, Bob Trivers' thesis - "Zoologiska Bidrag fran Uppsala"] [2 of 5] (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - [Document for UCSC, Bob Trivers' thesis - "Zoologiska Bidrag fran Uppsala"] [3 of 5] (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - [Document for UCSC, Bob Trivers' thesis - "Zoologiska Bidrag fran Uppsala"] [4 of 5] (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - [Document for UCSC, Bob Trivers' thesis - "Zoologiska Bidrag fran Uppsala"] [5 of 5] (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - [Document for UCSC, Bob Trivers' thesis - "IBN Battuta in Black Africa" by Said Hamdum and Noel King] [1 of 2] (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - [Document for UCSC, Bob Trivers' thesis - "IBN Battuta in Black Africa" by Said Hamdum and Noel King] [2 of 2] (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - [HPN Dissertation] [1 of 3] (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - [HPN Dissertation] [2 of 3] (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - [HPN Dissertation] [3 of 3] (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - [The War against the Panthers: A Study of Repression in America, by H. P. N]1980 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - [The War On the Panthers: An Overview] 1978 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - [HPN Dissertation on the Black Panthers] [1 of 2]1982 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - [HPN Dissertation on the Black Panthers] [2 of 2]1982 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Corrections to HPN Thesis (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - General Dissertation Info. [1 of 2] (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - General Dissertation Info. [2 of 2] (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence Re: Huey's Dissertation 8/26/811980 - 1982 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      AIM for Freedom Survival Group
    - University Of Santa Cruz - Commencement Program 6/15/801980 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Duplicates of Commencement Exercises 6/15/801980 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Huey Receiving PhD Newspaper Clipping (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Paul Lee 1980 (Box 46, Folder 7)
      Herbalism, Herbs
    - Graduate Theological Union Fall 1980-19811980 - 1981 (Box 46, Folder 8)
      Registration Information
    - Letters Between Bob Trivers and HPN (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Read for Book with Trivers [1 of 7]1976 - 1980 (Box 46, Folder 10)
      Autobiography of Charles Darwin;Note;Show Business (newspaper clipping);Totalitarian Ego
    - Read for Book with Trivers [2 of 7]1977 - 1981 (Box 46, Folder 11)
      Experiments in Overcoming Self-Deception;Psychology and the Lie Detector Industry;Hemisphericity, Cognitive Set, and Susceptibility to Subliminal Perception;Lying to Oneself;Autonomic Discrimination Without Awareness: A Study of Subception;Investigations of Repression: Differential Recall of Material Experimentally or Naturally Associated with Ego Threat;The K Factor as a Suppressor Variable in the Minnesota Multiphasic Personality Inventory;Role-Enactment and Deception Methodologies: Alternative Paradigms;The True Deceiver
    - Read for Book with Trivers [3 of 7]1977 - 1981 (Box 46, Folder 12)
      Environmental Structure and Cognitive Structure;The Totalitarian Ego: Gabrication and Revision of Personal History;Reconstructing the Past: Some Cognitive Consequences of Person Perception;Self-Deception: A Concept in Search of a Phenomenon
    - Read for Book with Trivers [4 of 7]1977 - 1981 (Box 46, Folder 13)
      Physiological Measures and the Detection of Deception;Attributed Intentions and Informational Selectivity;Traits as Prototypes: Effects on Recognition Memory;Perseverance in Self-Perception and Social Perception: Biased Attributional Processes in the Debriefing Paradigm;Sentence Memory: A Constructive Versus Interpretive Approach;Objective Use of Multiple Physiological Indices in the Detection of Deception;Illusory Correlation as an Obstacle to the Use of Valid Psychodiagnostic Signs;Genesis of Popular but Erroneous Psychodiagnostic Observations;Detecting Deception from the Body or Face;Function of Eyespot Patterns in the Lepidoptera;Some Experiments on the Camouflage of stick Caterpillars
    - Read for Book with Trivers [5 of 7]1977 - 1981 (Box 46, Folder 14)
      Physiological Measures and the Detection of Deception;Nonverbal Leakage and Clues to Deception;The Objective Use of Multiple Physiological Indices in the Detection of Deception;An Evaluation of Field Techniques in Detection of Deception;Natural Deception
    - Read for Book with Trivers [6 of 7]1977 - 1981 (Box 46, Folder 14)
      Selective Inattention;Effects of Age and Prior Help on "Altruistic Lying";Detecting Deception from the Body or Face;Adaptive Female-Mimicking Behavior in a Scorpionfly;An Exploratory Study of Pupillary Responses During Deception;Effects of Heightened Motivation on the Detection of Deception;The Effects of Task and Method of Stimulus Presentation on the Detection of Deception;The Ability to Judge Truth-Telling, or Lying, from the voice as Transmitted over a Public Address System;Ocular Stability in Deception;The Inspiration-Expieation Ratio During Truth and Falsehood;Changes of Blood Pressure and Respiration During Deception
    - Read for Book with Trivers [7 of 7]1977 - 1981 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      A History of Lie Detection;Modification of the Marston Deception Test;Reliability of Polygraph Examiner Diagnosis of Truth and Deception;Detection of Deception Technique Admitted as Evidence;Detection of Deception as a Function of Galvanic Skin Response Recording Methodology;Temporary False Belief;Psychology Abstracts
    - The Pursuit of Knowledge by Robert Trivers 1980 - 1981 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      [UCSC Hist Consc program booklet inclosed--used to date]
    - Method of Dialectical Materialism Equation (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Exhibits (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - [Bibliography information] (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - [One man's notes]1965 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      From a seminar with Saul Alinsky, Asilomar - September 1965
    - Diploma. Associates of Arts degree. Merritt College, Oakland, Calif. [Note: fragile]1966 June 17 (Othertype 61, Folder 1)
    - Diploma. Bachelor of Arts. University of California, Santa Cruz, Calif. [Note: fragile]1974 June 16 (Othertype 61, Folder 1)
    - Diploma. Doctor of Philosophy. University of California, Santa Cruz, Calif. [Note: extremely fragile]1980 June 13 (Othertype 61, Folder 3)
    - Huey Newton [art original] / Jon.d., 1 item; pencil on paper (Othertype 61, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 5: Manuscripts, 5
    - General Information Regarding the Servant's Books [1 of 2]1970 - 1972 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      Stronghold Consolidated Productions, Inc.
    - General Information Regarding the Servant's Books [2 of 2]1970 - 1972 (Box 47, Folder 7)
      The National Lawyers Guild Practitioner;The Rise and Future Demise of the World Capitalist System: Concepts for Comparative Analysis;Functional Definition of Politics
    - Info. On Books Written by Huey (Box 47, Folder 8)
      Peace Press Fall Books 1980;City Lights Publications
    - Servant Writings [1 of 2]1972-1973 (Box 47, Folder 9)
      Firing Line Transcript (1973);sample poll results
    - Servant Writings [2 of 2]1972-1973 (Box 47, Folder 10)
      sample poll results
    - HPN - Short Stories (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Insights Huey (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - H.P.N. Cuba (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - A Letter From Huey to the Revolutionary Brothers and Sisters1970 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - An Open Letter to Roy Wilkins (Box 47, Folder 15)
      Roy Wilkins "Wrong Priorities of Huey Newton"
    - Writings by HPN Exitentialism (Box 47, Folder 16)
      "The Historical Origins of Existentialism and the Common Denominators of Existential Philosophy"
    - ["Roots of Existenial Philosophy"]1978 (Box 47, Folder 17)
      "The Roots of Existential Philosophy in Western Thought";"Can Religion Survive?";"Tillich Acording to the Paucks"
    - The Real Black Panther Party by Huey P. Newton1972 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - A Force Against U.S. Imperialism, The Black Panther Party1970 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Towards a New Constitution by Huey P. Newton (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Black Capitalism Reanalyzed: A Theoretical Analyst and Its Practical Application by H. P. Newton1971 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - On "Pan Africanism or Communism" "Communism and Black Nationalism" (Box 47, Folder 22)
      [HPN Dec 72 typed]
    - "A Citizen's Peace Force" (Box 47, Folder 23)
      second draft, 2 copies
    - To the Courageous Revolutionaries of the National Liberation Front and Provisional Revolutionary... (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Prison Where is Thy Victory (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - H. P. Newton - The Prison, the Prisoner and Society - Gail Sheehy Ms - G. Jackson Article1970 - 1971 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - A Consistent Ideology1970 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      memo from J. Herman Blake
    - Intercommunalism a Higher Level of Consciousness by HPN (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - People's Revolutionary Intercommunalism [1 of 4]1967 - 1971 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      "Open Letter to Roy Wilkins" by Huey P. Newton, September 26, 1970
    - People's Revolutionary Intercommunalism [2 of 4]1967 - 1971 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - People's Revolutionary Intercommunalism [3 of 4]1967 - 1971 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - People's Revolutionary Intercommunalism [4 of 4]1967 - 1971 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - The Technology Question, by HPN (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - The Technology Question; After the Land Question1972 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - The Technology Question, by H.P. Newton 1972 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - The Technology Question, by Huey P. Newton 1972 1972 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Proposal - Original Draft - Eliminate the Presidency (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Eliminate the Presidency1974 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Defection of Eldridge Cleaver From the BPP: and the Defection of the BPP From the Community1971 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Hidden Traitor - Defection of E. Cleaver (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Hidden Traitor [1 of 2]1972 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Hidden Traitor [2 of 2]1972 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - [Short manuscript set in Vietnam] (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Unnamed script/Super Thief [1 of 2]1979 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Unnamed script/Super Thief [2 of 2]1979 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Proposed Movie Script (Box 49, Folder 4)
      "Blues for Huey";"Shotgun Politics in Sundown City"
    - "Punk-Hunting": Revised 1976 1976 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - [The Modern Day Porgy & Bess ] [1 of 4]1979 - 1980 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - [The Modern Day Porgy & Bess ] [2 of 4]1979 - 1980 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - [The Modern Day Porgy & Bess ] [3 of 4]1979 - 1980 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - [The Modern Day Porgy & Bess ] [4 of 4]1979 - 1980 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Huey P. Newton - Script Stinky! (handwritten)1979 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Berkeley Rapist Stinky - HPN (Manuscript) (Box 49, Folder 11)
      includes newspaper articles about the rapist
    - Berkeley Rapist Stinky 1977 (Box 49, Folder 12)
      includes newspaper and magazine articles about the rapist
    - Huey Newton - Essays1971 - 1973 (Box 49, Folder 13)
      publisher's agreements;one essay "TheParty"
    - Manuscript, by Huey P. Newton (first draft) Copyright 1974 by Huey P. Newton [1 of 4]1974 (Box 49, Folder 14)
      "Genesis Accordimg to Science"
    - Manuscript, by Huey P. Newton (first draft) Copyright 1974 by Huey P. Newton [2 of 4]1974 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      "The First Hero of Literature";""Second Isaiah" and the Mystery of the Servant
    - Manuscript, by Huey P. Newton (first draft) Copyright 1974 by Huey P. Newton [3 of 4]1973 - 1974 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      "The Son of Man";"The Dialectics of Nature";"The Technology Question";"The Functional Definition of Politic's";"Intercommunalism"
    - Manuscript, by Huey P. Newton (first draft) Copyright 1974 by Huey P. Newton [4 of 4]1972 - 1974 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      "Intercommunalism";"Oakland: an All-American Example";"Hidden Traitor Renegade Scab: Eldridge Cleaver"
    - A Revolutionary Analysis of Sweet Sweetback's Baadass Song, by Huey P. Newton, 1971 [1 of 2]1970 - 1971 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - A Revolutionary Analysis of Sweet Sweetback's Baadass Song, by Huey P. Newton, 1971 [2 of 2]1970 - 1971 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      photos of Melvin Van Peebles
    - In Search of Common Ground1973 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - To Die For the People [1 of 2]1972 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      reviews and publishers letters
    - To Die For the People [2 of 2]1972 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      publicity plans and publishers letters
    - The Opening Shot [1 of 2]1979 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - The Opening Shot [2 of 2]1979 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Huey's Logic of Self Deception [1 of 2] (Box 50, Folder 11)
      proposal and self-deception materials
    - Huey's Logic of Self Deception [2 of 2] (Box 51, Folder 1)
      self-deception materials
    - Deceipt and Self-Deception [1 of 3]1979 - 1981 (Box 51, Folder 2)
      letters, photos and examples of deceipt and self-deception
    - Deceipt and Self-Deception [2 of 3]1981 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      experimental study
    - Deceipt and Self-Deception [3 of 3]1979 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - The Real Dragon1979 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - [War Without Terms 1978]1978 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - War Without Terms Manuscript the Death of George Jackson 1979 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - War Without Terms: Death of George Jackson #2 [1 of 3] (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - War Without Terms: Death of George Jackson #2 [2 of 3] (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - War Without Terms: Death of George Jackson #2 [3 of 3] (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - [War without terms: the death of George Jackson]1978 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Signed Agreement Between Robert Trivers and Huey P. Newton 1/30/821982 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      regarding "Deceit and Self-Deception"
    - Molecular Level by Parasites by Bob Trivers1983 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      letter from Bob Trivers;Chapter 18 of "Deceit and Self-Deception"
    - Personal Letters to HPN1981 - 1982 (Box 52, Folder 5)
      letters to and from Robert Trivers;agreement regarding publications
    - Article: HPN & Professor Collaborate on Book About Deceipt 2/82 1982 (Box 52, Folder 6)
      newspaper article - "The Sentinal", Santa Cruz
    - Book with Trivers [1 of 13]1979 - 1981 (Box 52, Folder 7)
      letters, articles and research materials
    - Book with Trivers [2 of 13]1979 - 1981 (Box 52, Folder 8)
      "Parasitism Organic and Social" by Jean Massart
    - Book with Trivers [3 of 13]1979 - 1981 (Box 52, Folder 9)
      "The Fire Next Time" by Huey P. Newton;other reference articles
    - Book with Trivers [4 of 13]1979 - 1981 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      reference articles
    - Book with Trivers [5 of 13]1979 - 1981 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Book with Trivers [6 of 13]1979 - 1981 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Book with Trivers [7 of 13]1979 - 1981 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Book with Trivers [8 of 13]1979 - 1981 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Book with Trivers [9 of 13]1979 - 1981 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      "Princples of Social Evolution" by Bob Trivers;reference materials
    - Book with Trivers [10 of 13]1979 - 1981 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Book with Trivers [11 of 13]1979 - 1981 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      reference materials
    - Book with Trivers [12 of 13]1979 - 1981 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Book with Trivers [13 of 13]1979 - 1981 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - [Draft of Part I: Revolutionary Suicide + cover letter from Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, Inc.]1971 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - [Revolutionary Suicide - Draft] [1 of 5]1973 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - [Revolutionary Suicide - Draft] [2 of 5]1973 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - [Revolutionary Suicide - Draft] [3 of 5]1973 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - [Revolutionary Suicide - Draft] [4 of 5]1973 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - [Revolutionary Suicide - Draft] [5 of 5]1973 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - [Advanced copy of Revolutionary Suicide] [1 of 2] (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - [Advanced copy of Revolutionary Suicide] [2 of 2] (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Revolutionary Suicide - Originals [1 of 4]1972 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Revolutionary Suicide - Originals [2 of 4]1972 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Revolutionary Suicide - Originals [3 of 4]1972 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Revolutionary Suicide - Originals [4 of 4]1972 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Revolutionary Suicide1973 (Box 54, Folder 7)
      newspaper and magazine reviews and articles
    - Quotes, etc. Suicide1973 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Revolutionary Sucide - Huey P. Newton and the Panthers (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - H. Blake - H. Newton Book Contract, Harcourt, Brace, Jovanovich 1973 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - [Revolutionary Suicide]1973 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      advanced uncorrected proof
    - Summary: Revolutionary Suicide (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - These graves are all too young [1 of 3] (Box 55, Folder 3)
      Revolutionary Suicide part 3
    - These graves are all too young [2 of 3] (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - These graves are all too young [3 of 3] (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - [The War Against the Panthers - new outline] (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - [The War against the Panthers][1 of 2]1978 (Box 55, Folder 7)
      proposal
    - [The War against the Panthers][2 of 2]1978 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - [The War against the Panthers - Preliminary Draft]1978 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - [War on the Panthers][1 of 2] (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - [War on the Panthers][2 of 2] (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - [War against the Panthers - edited draft] [1 of 2] (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - [War against the Panthers - edited draft] [2 of 2] (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - [War on the Panthers: an overview] (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - The War Against the Panthers, by Huey P. Newton 19781978 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - War Against the Panthers - Manuscript [1 of 2]1978 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - War Against the Panthers - Manuscript [2 of 2]1978 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - The War Against the Panthers: An overview 1977/78 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - The War Against the Panthers: a study of repression in America1979 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Huey's Columbia contract1980 (Box 56, Folder 9)
      Peace Press
    - Law Book Lost by Huey P. Newton (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Books to be Written1978 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 6: Speeches/Lectures/Interviews, 6
    - Letters Requesting that Huey Speak1971 - 1972 (Box 57, Folder 1)